[WHISPERS INDISTINCTLY]
[CHUCKLES]
(Penny:)- What?
- Uh, he said maybe we should enter you...
...in the killer-robot competition.
[RAJESH CHUCKLING]
[PHONE RINGING]
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
Howard, the phone is ringing!
Here's a crazy idea, Ma: answer it!
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
Hello?
(Howard's Mother(voice):)All right, hold on.
(Howard's Mother(voice):)It's your friend, Leonard!
(Howard's Mother(voice):)He wants to know
why you're not at school today.
(Howard:)I don't go to school, Ma.
(Howard:)I work at a university.
MRS. WOLOWITZ: That's a school.
Now pick up the phone.
I don't wanna talk to anybody.
MRS. WOLOWITZ: Should I ask Leonard
to bring over your homework?
(Howard:)I don't have homework.